SHUBHAM MOURYA

UI/UX DESIGNER

<u>shubham.mourya148@gmail.com</u> +91 8885271197

Profile

I'm an experienced UI/UX Designer with four years at top companies like Verizon, TCS, and Right Data Labs. I focus on crafting intuitive interfaces, collaborating with stakeholders to enhance usability.

\sim	7	٠	7	7
ς.	1^	7	ı	Ιc
D	n.	L	L	Lわ

Focused	Interface Design	Programming	
Design Thinking	Wireframing	HTML	
User Centric Design	User Centric Design	CSS	
User Flows	User Flows	Javascript	

Experience

Verizon

Engineer-II UI/UX Designer

Jan, 2024 - Present

As a UI/UX Designer at Verizon, I am tasked with elevating the user experience (UX) and interface design of internal products, focusing on enhancing usability, functionality, and visual appeal.

Right Data Labs Pvt Ltd. UI/UX Designer

Dec, 2022 - Dec, 2023

Led UI/UX design for DataFactory and DataMarket, an all-encompassing data management platform covering migration, orchestration, DataOps, and reporting. Collaborated with stakeholders, enhancing usability by delivering intuitive, user-friendly interfaces.

Simplified complex data tasks with visual ETL, ELT, and lake house operations. Integrated machine learning for user-friendly segmentation and categorization. Empowered users with swift data governance through APIs and JDBC connectors. Improved data access and actionability via a user-friendly interface, featuring natural language search and data quality assessment.

Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) UI/UX Designer

Feb, 2020 - Oct, 2022

Working on user Research, user flows, wireframes, designing user interfaces, and developing prototypes for new features. Iterating efficient designs based on business requirements, technology constraints, and user feedback.

Playing a role in improving the user experience of a International CITI Bank. Collaborated with crossfunctional teams to ensure consistent branding and visual design across the product.

Education

Google UX Design Certificate

June 2021 - March 2022

Certificate: https://www.credly.com/go/nAB4um5U

Osmania University - B.sc Computer Science June 2016 - June 2019 — **7.5** CGPA